gamesxite.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Big Fish Games, Inc.

Last modified: April 14, 2014

We at Big Fish have created this Privacy Policy to describe the treatment of information provided or collected via Big Fish Offerings.  **By accessing and/or using this Big Fish website or any Big Fish Offering, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

The term **"Big Fish"** means Big Fish Games, Inc. and/or its Affiliates. The term **"Affiliate"** means, with respect to any party, any person or entity which controls, is controlled by, or is under common control with, such party. The term **"Big Fish Offering"** means the websites of Big Fish, including [www.bigfishgames.com](http://www.bigfishgames.com/), [www.selfawaregames.com](http://www.selfawaregames.com/), any other sites on which this Privacy Policy is posted, and any other Big Fish application, service or product licensed, downloaded or otherwise accessed by you through third party sites or sources, including the products and services available through any of the foregoing.

## INFORMATION THAT WE MAY COLLECT

### Personally Identifiable Information:

We may collect the following information when you sign up with a Big Fish Offering: first name, last name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit or debit card information or other payment details, depending on your form of payment.

### Technical Information:

When a user accesses a Big Fish Offering, we may collect technical information about the user’s device, such as the IP address that requested the display of the Big Fish Offering, the operating system type, and the device identifier.

### Sign Up and Survey information:

Any information you provide to us, and any information you choose to share about yourself as part of your use of any Big Fish Offering, may be stored as entered.

### Cookies and Web beacons:

Cookies are text files that we and our service providers may place on your device's browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your shopping cart between visits, personalized Big Fish advertisements on third party websites and mobile applications, and personalized third party advertisements within certain Big Fish Offerings. We may use Adobe Flash cookies to remember your settings, preferences and usage within a Big Fish Offering. Web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies are small pieces of code that we and our service providers may place on a Big Fish Offering to monitor and collect data about visitor behavior within the Big Fish Offering.

### Other Information Collected:

We may receive a confirmation when you open email from Big Fish, if your computer supports such capabilities. We may also track other types of information, such as what games users download and install, any download errors, what games users purchase, how long our users have been participating in any Big Fish Offerings, the last time a user accessed a Big Fish Offering, user behavior and gameplay, whether a user has won any of our games, sweepstakes, contests or other promotions featured on a Big Fish Offering, ad response measurement and other Big Fish Offerings analytics.

### Social Networking Sites:

If you access a Big Fish Offering via a third party social networking site (a " **Social Game** "), Big Fish may receive information about your social networking site profile, including without limitation the information you make publicly available, your social networking site user ID, your first, last and user names, profile and cover photos. If you invite new members into your Social Games network or send messages through Social Games, we may collect the information associated with those messages, including your friends' social networking site user IDs, email addresses and content.

### Mobile:

When you download or access Big Fish Offerings via a mobile device, we may receive information about your location (based on your IP address) and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device, hardware type, the version of your operating system and your in-game activity. We may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising and other personalized content. Most mobile devices allow you to turn off location services. If you have questions about how to disable your device's location services, you should contact your mobile service carrier or your device manufacturer.

### Aggregated, Anonymous Information:

We may collect aggregated, anonymized information via Big Fish Offerings that does not identify any single user.

## SECURITY OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

We collect and use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy for our legitimate business purposes. Big Fish uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you transmit to us. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. You should protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

## USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

We may use your username, email address, and password to uniquely identify you as a user on a Big Fish Offering, to provide you with services and to process transactions. We may use or display your username and icon or profile photo, if applicable, for the purposes of rankings, competitions or sweepstakes, chat identification, and/or game high scores.

Subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy, we may use your contact information to process our promotional newsletters and/or email campaigns and to send you updates, security alerts, or administrative messages relating to Big Fish Offerings. Your contact information will allow us to notify you about new features, enhancements, resolution of Big Fish Offerings problems, handle and/or route your customer support questions and issues, and inform you of upgrade opportunities, sweepstakes, contests, prizes, and/or special events.

If our "Tell a friend" feature is available within a particular Big Fish Offering and you choose to participate in it, your email will be shared with the person to whom you send the Big Fish Offering using this feature. We may use an IP address to surface the appropriate country-based version of a Big Fish Offering to a user, or to exercise our ability to restrict access to the site by users who have violated our Terms of Use.

We and our third party service providers use cookies to enhance your online experience. The information in cookies enables us to run our affiliate programs and provide you with customized content or offerings, such as personalized Big Fish advertisements on other websites and mobile applications and personalized third party advertisements within certain Big Fish Offerings. Cookies also enable you to automatically sign in when you access a Big Fish Offering, and offer other operational activities within a Big Fish Offering. We and our third party service providers may also use cookies to manage and measure the performance of third party advertisements within certain Big Fish Offerings, and Big Fish advertisements on third party sites and mobile applications. This helps us and our service providers provide more relevant advertising to you. We and our third party service providers may also use web beacons to monitor user behavior and collect information about visitors viewing a web page.

We may use other identifying information collected to calculate aggregate, anonymized statistics about our user community for the purpose of enhancing our Big Fish Offerings, or for security purposes.

If you access a Social Game, we may use your social networking site profile ID to link your social networking site account with your activities within the Social Game or offer personalized Big Fish advertisements on the social networking site. We may use your social networking site first, last and user names and icon to identify you to the social networking site account you've linked to your activities within the Social Game, as well as for the purposes of rankings, competitions, sweepstakes, game high scores and/or identification to your social network.

If you access a Social Game and provide us with another person's contact information for purposes of delivering information through a Social Game, we may use this information to contact and, if necessary, remind that person that she or he has been invited to join a Social Game or received content through a Social Game. All invitees are provided with the option not to receive further invitations from Big Fish.

## SHARING INFORMATION

We may share customer information with Big Fish Affiliates, and as described below.

### Third Party Service Providers:

We may disclose your personal information as well as aggregate, anonymous information to third party business partners and third parties who perform services for us, such as credit card processing, prize fulfillment, delivering packages, sending postal mail, collecting and analyzing data, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), and providing advertising and marketing assistance, including serving ads on our behalf on third party websites and serving ads on behalf of third parties within certain Big Fish Offerings. Those third parties have access to your information only as necessary to perform their functions, and for no other purposes.

### Business Transfers:

As Big Fish continues to grow, we might sell or buy certain subsidiaries and/or business units. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred assets. Also, in the unlikely event that Big Fish or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information would in most cases be one of the transferred assets.

### Protection of Big Fish and Others:

We may also disclose your information if there is a violation of the [Terms of Use](http://www.bigfishgames.com/company/terms.html) or other agreements; if we have a good faith belief that the law requires it; or if needed to protect the rights, property or safety of Big Fish, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with entities for fraud detection and protection, and credit risk reduction.

## YOUR CHOICES

### Promotional email communications:

When you create a customer account or provide access to your email address via a Big Fish Offering, you may be automatically registered to receive one or more of our promotional e- newsletters, even if you previously opted out of receiving newsletters at a previous time. If you express interest in a Big Fish Offering by clicking on a banner within a newsletter, you may be automatically registered to receive newsletters relating to the Big Fish Offering that appeared in the banner. At any time, you may opt-out of receiving a newsletter by selecting the " **unsubscribe** " link at the bottom of any newsletter. We treat each Big Fish Offering individually, so if you are receiving mailings from more than one Big Fish Offering, if you want to unsubscribe you must do so with respect to each individually. Please note that we reserve the right to send you non-promotional, account or administrative emails even if you opt out of receiving promotional e-newsletters.

### Cookies, Online Advertising and Analytics:

Please refer to your browser settings and help section to learn about blocking, erasing or being notified of cookies. You can manage your Flash cookies by using Adobe's Flash management tools [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Big Fish Offerings' essential features, we recommend that you leave cookies turned on. For example, you may not be able make purchases on Big Fish Offerings without having cookies turned on. To opt out of receiving personalized advertising from many ad networks, data exchanges, marketing analytics and other services providers who are members of the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) (NAI) or the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/) (DAA), please visit the opt-out pages of the NAI or DAA websites. To opt out of the use of your personal information for third party analytics purposes, please email us at [privacy@bigfishgames.com](mailto:privacy@bigfishgames.com).

### Social Games:

With respect to Social Games, you may manage your own social network privacy preferences through your social networking site account.

### Contact Us:

To review, modify or remove the information you have provided to us, or to contact us with any questions or complaints, please email us at [privacy@bigfishgames.com](mailto:privacy@bigfishgames.com) or write to us at: Big Fish Privacy Policy Department, 333 Elliott Avenue West, Suite 200, Seattle, WA 98119 USA.

## THIRD-PARTY MARKETPLACES, ADVERTISERS AND LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES

If you access a Big Fish Offering via a third party marketplace, such as Apple’s App Store, that third party marketplace may collect information about you or receive information from us in order to provide or analyze its services. In addition, third parties that serve advertisements within certain Big Fish Offerings and/or serve Big Fish advertisements on third party websites and mobile applications, as well as third party links to or from a Big Fish Offering, may collect information about you. If you access our Social Games, this includes, without limitation, any social networking sites that you participate in. Most content offered through Social Games is served or hosted by other websites. Big Fish does not provide any personal information to those third parties, and Big Fish has no control over, and is not responsible for, the information submitted to or collected by third parties. We encourage you to review those third party privacy policies to understand the way your information may be collected and handled by such third parties.

## CHAT & MESSAGING

Big Fish Offerings may operate message boards and/or chat areas where users can exchange ideas and communicate with each other. When posting to a message board or chat area, the information is being made publicly available in an online environment. Any information posted is the sole responsibility of the individual user.

## CHILDREN

We at Big Fish do not offer products for purchase by children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children. If you are under 13, you may use and access the Big Fish Offerings only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

Big Fish respects the privacy of parents and children and is committed to complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to Big Fish, he or she can contact us via email at [privacy@bigfishgames.com](mailto:privacy@bigfishgames.com) or postal mail at: Big Fish Privacy Policy Department, 333 Elliott Avenue West, Suite 200, Seattle, WA 98119 USA. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13. We recognize the importance of safeguarding the privacy of children and encourage parents to check and monitor their children's use of online activities regularly.

## SAFE HARBOR PROGRAM

We may transfer, store and/or process personal information in the U.S. or in other countries. Big Fish complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. For more information about the Safe Harbor program and to view our certification, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's [Safe Harbor Website](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/). To contact Big Fish directly about the Safe Harbor program, please email us at [safeharbor@bigfishgames.com](mailto:safeharbor@bigfishgames.com). Please note that if you are located in the E.U., Switzerland or other region with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, you are transferring information to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction.

## AGREEMENT WITH BIG FISH POLICIES

By accessing and/or using any of the Big Fish Offerings, you signify your understanding of and agreement with this Privacy Policy, and to our [Terms of Use](http://www.bigfishgames.com/company/terms.html). If you do not agree with our policies, please do not access or use any Big Fish Offerings.

## CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last modified" date at the top of this page. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how Big Fish protects your information.
